<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wayfar</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="Dashboard_Intro">Uttarakhand is a state in the northern part of India. It is often referred to as the Devbhumi, the Land of the Gods due to its religious significance and numerous Hindu temples and pilgrimage sites found throught the state. Uttarakhand is famous for Chota Char Dham, which literally meaning journey to four centres. These four religious centers in Uttarakhand are represented by Badrinath(dedicated to Lord Vishnu), Kedarnath(dedicated to Lord Shiva), Gangotri(the holy origin of river Ganga) and Yamunotri(the holy origin of river Yamuna). Badrinath is part of the bigger Char Dham. While these are the most famous ones there are many more beautiful places and temples to visit in Uttarakhand. Some of these include Bansi Narayan Temple, Someshwar Temple, Basukedar Temple, Valley of Flowers and many more.</string>
    <string name="Dashboard_AboutUs">This app intends to publicize such hidden temples and famous places to visit in Uttarakhand which most of the people are unaware of. We provide all the information about such places and also the places to visit near them. You can also use the google maps to travel to those places from the app itself. We also provide all the travelling options to reach the destination. You can find all the info by clicking on the  toogle button on the top left corner followed by selecting the destination.</string>
    <string name="Badrinath_Intro">Badrinath Temple is situated in Chamoli district in the state of Uttarakhand, India. It is a Hindu holy place, and is one of the four sites in India\'s Char Dham pilgrimage. It is also part of India\'s Chota Char Dham pilgrimage circuit. The temple in Badrinath is also a sacred pilgrimage site for Vaishnavites. Badrinath is also gateway to several mountaineering expeditions headed to mountains like Nilkantha. &#xA; &#xA; According to legend, Adi Shankaracharya discovered a black stone image of Lord Badrinarayan made of Shaligram stone in the Alaknanda River. He originally enshrined it in a cave near the Tapt Kund hot springs. In the sixteenth century, the King of Garhwal moved the murti to the present temple.</string>
    <string name="Badrinath_History">Badrinath is associated with Lord Vishnu, one of the principal deities in the Hindu pantheon. It is believed to be one of the four Char Dham pilgrimage sites, with the other three being Kedarnath, Gangotri, and Yamunotri. The Char Dham Yatra is an important pilgrimage for Hindus, and visiting these sites is considered highly auspicious. &#xA; &#xA; Badrinath is a destination for pilgrims and tourists alike. The temple attracts devotees from all over India and even beyond. The sacred Alaknanda River flows near the temple, and the surrounding landscapes offer breathtaking views of the Himalayan mountains. The town comes to life during the pilgrimage season, which typically runs from late April to early November. </string>






    <string name="Basukedar_Intro"> Basukedar Temple, a highly revered temple dedicated to Lord Shiva, is located at the peaceful village of Basukedar in Rudraprayag district of Uttarakhand.

The entire region around the temple is a spiritual haven for yoga practitioners, travellers, and spiritual seekers. The temple is surrounded by beautiful Himalayan views, with the most notable being the Chaukhamba Peak (7,138 meters) to the north.

This magnificent temple is carved in stone with captivating premises and views. There are small shrines around the main temple whose architecture and strategic placements beautifully enchances the ambience of the place. The temple complex has the main temple dedicated to Lord Shiva, and about 25 other smaller temples of various gods and goddesses.
    </string>

    <string name="Basukedar_History">Basukedar Temple is a Shiva temple and its architecture seems to be at least 1000 yrs old. In earlier times, the route leading to this temple served as the original route to Kedarnath, when roads were not constructed. It is said that Lord Shiva stayed a night in Basukedar while he was travelling to Mount Kailash (Kedarnath) and hence the reason that this village is called Basukedar.

Another belief is that the temple was constructed by the Pandavas, on their way to search for Lord Shiva, in hopes that he would release them of their sins of committing genocide. The place is believed to be the last place where Lord Shiva was seen.
    </string>

    <string name="Basukedar_attraction">Basukedar is a not a hill station nevertheless it gives a glimpse of Himalayas, including activities such as trekking and a scenic landscape dotted with snow covered peak hills and forests. This is one of the most famous attractions during peak summer and fall winter time. Many of highest peaks in the region and magnificent views of the Himalayan ranges can be seen from the top. Chandrapuri , a nearby station at NH-58, joined by an old track to get transportation. it is connected with a road which comes from Agustyamuni and linked to Guptkashi</string>




    <string name="Someshwar_Intro">Someshwar Temple, dedicated to Lord Shiva, is located in the beautiful Someshwar Valley in Almora district of Uttarakhand. This temple is one of the religious and spiritual place in Uttarakhand. It attracts not only devotees but also tourists who wish to experience nature’s beauty and colourful culture of Uttarakhand. The valley lies on the bank of Kosi and Sai River and consists of quaint hamlets surrounded by natural beauty all around.</string>






</resources>

